# Sean DeBuys

Evanston, IL - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Sean-DeBuys/cd23e9128a1fabf1

Materials Science and Engineering graduate with material analysis experience using methods such as TGA, DSC, SEM, metallography preparation, tensile testing, impact testing, and hardness testing. Familiar with product design and development through senior design project.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Android Game Developer**

DeBuysDev - Evanston, IL - February 2016 to Present

Coded and developed an Android app game called Poly-Ship which was released to the Google Play Store
in May

2017.

• Currently developing other apps with separate, and more complex, game mechanisms.

## Splashpark Manager

City of Roswell Recreation and Parks Department - Roswell, GA - May 2014 to September 2015

- Managed a total of 15 staff members that worked to ensure the rules and policies of the park.
- Handled a cash flow of over 500 dollars a day.
- Regulated pH and chemical levels of the water daily.
- Maintained the filtration system, pumps, chemical hoppers, and facility.
- Coordinated rentals and parties held at the facility.
- Assisted in scheduling of work for staff.

## Member

Interface, Inc. - LaGrange, GA - January 2015 to May 2015

- Worked with Interface Inc. and 5 person team to solve an engineering problem of researching a new carpet backing material that is recyclable and environmentally friendly.
- Researched a total of 7 different elastomers and thermoplastics using TGA, DSC, and APA testing.
- Developed options of EPDM rubber or recycled HDPE to look into further.

#### **Splashpark Attendant**

City of Roswell Recreation and Parks Department - Roswell, GA - May 2010 to August 2012

- Ensured that more than 250 children and adults followed the rules and safety regulations of the park each day.

#### **EDUCATION**

### **BS in Materials Science & Engineering**

Georgia Institute of Technology - Atlanta, GA August 2011 to December 2015

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Affiliations: Kappa Sigma Fraternity

Activities: Wreck Racing, Georgia Tech Crew Fall 2012

Volunteer: St. Andrew Rowing Club Summer Learn to Row Camp, St. Andrew Catholic Church